[
    {
        "question": "Click on Afghanistan.",
        "answer": "AF"
    },
    {
        "question": "Click on Brazil.",
        "answer": "BR"
    },
    {
        "question": "Click on India.",
        "answer": "IN"
    },
    {
        "question": "Click on Canada.",
        "answer": "CA"
    },
    {
        "question": "Click on Australia.",
        "answer": "AU"
    },
    {
        "question": "Click on Germany.",
        "answer": "DE"
    },
    {
        "question": "Click on South Africa.",
        "answer": "ZA"
    },
    {
        "question": "Click on France.",
        "answer": "FR"
    },
    {
        "question": "Click on China.",
        "answer": "CN"
    },
    {
        "question": "Click on Egypt.",
        "answer": "EG"
    },
    {
        "question": "Click on Saudi Arabia.",
        "answer": "SA"
    },
    {
        "question": "Click on the United States.",
        "answer": "US"
    },
    {
        "question": "Click on Japan.",
        "answer": "JP"
    },
    {
        "question": "Click on Russia.",
        "answer": "RU"
    },
    {
        "question": "Click on Mexico.",
        "answer": "MX"
    },
    {
        "question": "Click on Argentina.",
        "answer": "AR"
    },
    {
        "question": "Click on Italy.",
        "answer": "IT"
    },
    {
        "question": "Click on Spain.",
        "answer": "ES"
    },
    {
        "question": "Click on Nigeria.",
        "answer": "NG"
    },
    {
        "question": "Click on Turkey.",
        "answer": "TR"
    }
]
